(this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz"]||[]).push([[0],{121:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n.p+"static/media/logo.ee9e8b1b.svg"},124:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(282)},129:function(e,t,n){},279:function(e,t,n){},282:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var r=n(0),o=n.n(r),a=n(76),i=n.n(a),c=n(51),s=(n(129),n(27)),l=n(28),u=n(29),p=n(32),m=n(30),d=n(46),y=n(33),h=n(8),f=[{question:"What decade did formal research in AI begin ?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"1950s"},{type:"incorrect",content:"1960s"},{type:"incorrect",content:"1980s"},{type:"incorrect",content:"2000s "}]},{question:"The area of AI that investigates on methods of facilitating communication between people and computer is :",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Machine learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Symbolic processing"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision Support"},{type:"correct",content:"Natural language processing"}]},{question:"The practice of using algorithms to parse data, learn from it, and then make a determination or prediction about something is :",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"Machine learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Symbolic processing"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision Support"},{type:"incorrect",content:"None of These"}]},{question:"Which of the following methods is NOT a learning method ?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Memorization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Analogy"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Deduction"},{type:"correct",content:"Introduction"}]},{question:"Which programming language is commonly used for AI?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Boa"},{type:"correct",content:"Python"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Viper"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Cobra"}]},{question:"Who is considered as the \u201cfather\u201d of artificial intelligence?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"Donald Trump"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Kim Jong-Un"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Vladimir Poutine"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Alan Turing"}]},{question:"What is the goal of artificial intelligence?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"To solve real-world problems"},{type:"incorrect",content:"To solve artificial problems"},{type:"correct",content:"To explain various sorts of intelligence"},{type:"incorrect",content:"To extract scientific causes"}]},{question:"How does a decision tree make a decision ?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"After a single test"},{type:"incorrect",content:"After two tests"},{type:"correct",content:"After a sequence of tests"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Without a test"}]},{question:"What takes an object described by a set of attributes as input?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Random forest"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision graph"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision tree"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"What are the tasks an AI system can perform?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Act as a virtual assistant"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Automate manual processes"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Analyze unstructured data"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"Software designed to simulate a conversation between a computer and a human enduser is called a :",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"ChatBot"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Scream"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Sharepoint"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Walkie Talkie"}]},{question:"While evaluating a classifier\u2019s performance, what do we mean by the \u2018sensitivity\u2019 of our model?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"False positive rate"},{type:"correct",content:"True positive rate"},{type:"incorrect",content:"False negative rate"},{type:"incorrect",content:"True negative rate"}]},{question:"Which of the following is true about model capacity (the ability of a neural network to approximate complex functions)?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"As number of hidden layers increase, model capacity increases"},{type:"incorrect",content:"As dropout ratio increases, model capacity increases"},{type:"incorrect",content:"As learning rate increases, model capacity increases"},{type:"incorrect",content:"None of these"}]},{question:"What is(are) an(some) advantage(s) of decision trees?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Possible Scenarios can be added"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Interpretability of the model"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Worst, best and expected values can be determined for different scenarios"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"In unsupervised learning :",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Specific output values are given"},{type:"correct",content:"Output values are not given"},{type:"incorrect",content:"No specific inputs are given"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Both inputs and outputs are given"}]},{question:"Neural Networks are mainly used for modeling complex ______________with many parameters",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Linear Functions "},{type:"correct",content:"Nonlinear Functions"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Discrete Functions"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Exponential Functions"}]},{question:"What is a perceptron?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"a single layer feed-forward neural network with pre-processing"},{type:"incorrect",content:"an auto-associative neural network"},{type:"incorrect",content:"a double layer auto-associative neural network "},{type:"incorrect",content:"a neural network that contains feedback"}]},{question:"In which of the following learning paradigm the agent receives rewards and punishements based on the outcome?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Active Learning"},{type:"correct",content:"Reinforcement Learning "},{type:"incorrect",content:"Supervised learning "},{type:"incorrect",content:"Unsupervised learning"}]},{question:"Decision trees are appropriate for the problems where : ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"The output is numerical"},{type:"incorrect",content:"The output is nominal categorical"},{type:"incorrect",content:"The output is ordinal categorical "},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned "}]},{question:"How can back propagation be defined ? ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Another name given to the curvy function "},{type:"incorrect",content:"The transmission of error back through the network to adjust the inputs "},{type:"correct",content:"The transmission of error back through the network to adjust weights "},{type:"incorrect",content:"None of these"}]},{question:"What text mining technique can be used for noise reduction?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Lemmatization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Word embeddings"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Stemming"},{type:"correct",content:"Lemmatization and stemming"}]},{question:"What is the most efficient way of handling missing or corrupted categorical data in terms of information loss reduction?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Drop missing rows or columns"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Replace missing values with mean, median, and mode"},{type:"correct",content:"Assign a unique category to missing values"},{type:"incorrect",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"Which of the following is enabled by the kernel trick?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Regularization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Non-linear flexibility"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Variance of the estimator reduction"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"What technique(s) could be used to adjust the parameters and minimize the cost function?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Exhaustive Search"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Random Search"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Bayesian Optimization"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"What could be the reason for the loss to not decrease in the first few epochs while training a neural network?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"The learning rate is low"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Regularization parameter is high"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Stuck at local minima"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"What regularization process(es) enable(s) deep neural architectures training?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Batch normalization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"ELU activation functions"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Fully convolutionnal layers "},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"Computational learning theory analyzes the sample complexity and computational complexity of :",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Unsupervised Learning"},{type:"correct",content:"Inductive learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Forced based learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Weak learning"}]},{question:"If a decision process outputs positive evidence to reject an hypothesis, but in reality the hypothesis holds, it is a: ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Type II error"},{type:"incorrect",content:"False negative"},{type:"correct",content:"Type I error"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Specialized hypothesis"}]},{question:"Which of the following is also called exploratory learning?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Supervised learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Active learning "},{type:"correct",content:"Unsupervised learning "},{type:"incorrect",content:"Reinforcement learning "}]},{question:"In language processing, which levels of knowledge are not included?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Semantical"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Syntactical"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Pragmatical"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"How is the process of deleting certain neurons at random during the training of a neural network called?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Random subsampling"},{type:"correct",content:"Dropout"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Batch normalization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Neural killing"}]},{question:"What name(s) can be given to some decision tree nodes?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision Nodes"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Leaves"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Chance Nodes"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"Which of these does NOT use machine learning/AI?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Driverless cars"},{type:"incorrect",content:"SIRI"},{type:"correct",content:"Sonos wireless speakers"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Facial recognition on phone"}]},{question:"AI has a conscience ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"True"},{type:"correct",content:"False "},{type:"incorrect",content:"Maybe"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Depend of cases"}]},{question:"Which one of these is not an area of AI?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Computer Vison"},{type:"correct",content:"Web design"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Robotics"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Voice recognition"}]},{question:"Why is Weight Initialization important in Neural Networks? ",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"To prevent gradient from vanishing during the course of a backward pass "},{type:"incorrect",content:"To increase the accuracy of the model"},{type:"incorrect",content:"To use memory more efficiently "},{type:"incorrect",content:"For regularization purposes "}]}];f.forEach((function(e,t){return e.answers.forEach((function(e,n){"incorrect"===e.type&&(e.type="incorrect-".concat(t,"-").concat(n))}))}));var g=f,w=n(19);var v=function(e){return o.a.createElement("h2",{className:"question"},e.content)};var b=function(e){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionCount"},"Question ",o.a.createElement("span",null,e.counter)," of ",o.a.createElement("span",null,e.total))};var q=function(e){return o.a.createElement("li",{className:"answerOption"},o.a.createElement("input",{type:"radio",className:"radioCustomButton",name:"radioGroup",checked:e.answerType===e.answer,id:e.answerType,value:e.answerType,disabled:e.answer,onChange:e.onAnswerSelected}),o.a.createElement("label",{className:"radioCustomLabel",htmlFor:e.answerType},e.answerContent))};var E=function(e){return o.a.createElement(w.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500},o.a.createElement("div",{key:e.questionId},o.a.createElement(b,{counter:e.questionId,total:e.questionTotal}),o.a.createElement(v,{content:e.question}),o.a.createElement("ul",{className:"answerOptions"},e.answerOptions.map((function(t,n){return o.a.createElement(q,{key:t.content,index:n,answerContent:t.content,answerType:t.type,answer:e.answer,questionId:e.questionId,onAnswerSelected:e.onAnswerSelected})})))))},k=n(113),A=function(e){var t=e.formErrors;return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"formErrors"},Object.keys(t).map((function(e,n){return t[e].length>0?o.a.createElement("p",{style:{color:"red"},key:n},e," ",t[e]):""})))},S=n(284),T=n(285),O=n(286),N=n(287),x=function(e){function t(e){var n;return Object(l.a)(this,t),(n=Object(p.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).call(this,e))).handleUserInput=function(e){var t=e.target.name,r=e.target.value;n.setState(Object(s.a)({},t,r),(function(){n.validateField(t,r)}))},n.state={email:"",formErrors:{email:""},emailValid:!1,formValid:!1},n}return Object(y.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"validateField",value:function(e,t){var n=this.state.formErrors,r=this.state.emailValid;switch(e){case"email":r=t.match(/^([\w.%+-]+)@([\w-]+\.)+([\w]{2,})$/i),n.email=r?"":" is invalid"}this.setState({formErrors:n,emailValid:r},this.validateForm)}},{key:"validateForm",value:function(){this.setState({formValid:this.state.emailValid})}},{key:"errorClass",value:function(e){return 0===e.length?"":"has-error"}},{key:"formPreventDefault",value:function(e){e.preventDefault()}},{key:"storeWinnerEmail",value:function(){var e=this.state.email,t=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("emails"))||[];t.push(e),localStorage.setItem("emails",JSON.stringify(t)),document.location.reload()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=Object.keys(this.props.answersCount),t={labels:["Correct","Incorrect"],datasets:[{data:[this.props.answersCount.correct,e.filter((function(e){return"correct"!==e})).length],backgroundColor:["#cfde00","#0071ce"]}]};return o.a.createElement("form",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center",alignItems:"center",flexDirection:"column"},onSubmit:this.formPreventDefault},o.a.createElement("h2",null,"Congratulations, you have won the quizz !"),o.a.createElement(k.a,{data:t,options:{responsive:!0,maintainAspectRatio:!0}}),o.a.createElement("h3",null,"Share your score on social media !"),o.a.createElement("div",{style:{display:"flex"}},o.a.createElement(S.a,{url:"https://twitter.com/Qiminfo",hashtags:["AMLD2020","QimQuizz","Qiminfo"]},o.a.createElement(T.a,{size:64,round:!0})),o.a.createElement(O.a,{url:"https://www.linkedin.com/company/qim-info"},o.a.createElement(N.a,{size:64,round:!0}))),o.a.createElement("h3",null,"Please type your email in order to partifcipate to the draw and win an iPad"),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"form-group ".concat(this.errorClass(this.state.formErrors.email))},o.a.createElement("label",{htmlFor:"email"},"Email address"),o.a.createElement("input",{type:"email",required:!0,className:"form-control",name:"email",placeholder:"Email",value:this.state.email,onChange:this.handleUserInput,style:{width:"100%",padding:"12px 20px",margin:"8px 0",boxSizing:"border-box",fontSize:"16px",fontFamily:"PT Sans, sans-serif",borderRadius:"4px"}})),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"panel panel-default"},o.a.createElement(A,{formErrors:this.state.formErrors})),o.a.createElement("button",{style:{background:"#0071ce",border:"none",color:"white",padding:"15px 32px",textAlign:"center",textDecoration:"none",display:"inline-block",fontSize:"16px",fontFamily:"PT Sans, sans-serif",borderRadius:"4px"},className:"btn btn-primary",disabled:!this.state.formValid,onClick:this.storeWinnerEmail.bind(this)},"Submit"))}}]),t}(r.Component),z=function(){return window.location.reload()};var C=function(e){var t;return"lost"===e.quizResult&&(t=o.a.createElement("div",null,o.a.createElement("p",null,"You failed the quizz..."),o.a.createElement("button",{style:{background:"#0071ce",border:"none",color:"white",padding:"15px 32px",textAlign:"center",textDecoration:"none",display:"inline-block",fontSize:"16px",fontFamily:"PT Sans, sans-serif",borderRadius:"4px"},onClick:z}," Try again ?"))),"win"===e.quizResult&&(t=o.a.createElement(x,e)),o.a.createElement(w.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container result",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500},t)},I=n(121),j=n.n(I);n(279);function W(e,t){var n=Object.keys(e);if(Object.getOwnPropertySymbols){var r=Object.getOwnPropertySymbols(e);t&&(r=r.filter((function(t){return Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(e,t).enumerable}))),n.push.apply(n,r)}return n}function D(e){for(var t=1;t<arguments.length;t++){var n=null!=arguments[t]?arguments[t]:{};t%2?W(n,!0).forEach((function(t){Object(s.a)(e,t,n[t])})):Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors?Object.defineProperties(e,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors(n)):W(n).forEach((function(t){Object.defineProperty(e,t,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(n,t))}))}return e}var R=function(e){function t(e){var n;return Object(l.a)(this,t),(n=Object(p.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).call(this,e))).state={counter:0,questionId:1,question:"",answerOptions:[],answer:"",answersCount:{},result:"",questionsCount:10,quizzTitle:"Qim Quizz"},n.handleAnswerSelected=n.handleAnswerSelected.bind(Object(d.a)(n)),n}return Object(y.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){var e=this,t=this.shuffleArray(g),n=t.map((function(t){return e.shuffleArray(t.answers)}));this.setState({question:t[0].question,answerOptions:n[0]})}},{key:"shuffleArray",value:function(e){for(var t,n,r=e.length;0!==r;)n=Math.floor(Math.random()*r),t=e[r-=1],e[r]=e[n],e[n]=t;return e}},{key:"handleAnswerSelected",value:function(e){var t=this;this.setUserAnswer(e.currentTarget.value),this.state.questionId<this.state.questionsCount?setTimeout((function(){return t.setNextQuestion()}),300):setTimeout((function(){return t.setResults(t.getResults())}),300)}},{key:"setUserAnswer",value:function(e){this.setState((function(t,n){return{answersCount:D({},t.answersCount,Object(s.a)({},e,(t.answersCount[e]||0)+1)),answer:e}}))}},{key:"setNextQuestion",value:function(){var e=this.state.counter+1,t=this.state.questionId+1;this.setState({counter:e,questionId:t,question:g[e].question,answerOptions:g[e].answers,answer:""})}},{key:"getResults",value:function(){return this.state.answersCount.correct>=this.state.questionsCount/2?"win":"lost"}},{key:"setResults",value:function(e){this.setState({result:e})}},{key:"renderQuiz",value:function(){return o.a.createElement(E,{answer:this.state.answer,answerOptions:this.state.answerOptions,questionId:this.state.questionId,question:this.state.question,questionTotal:this.state.questionsCount,onAnswerSelected:this.handleAnswerSelected})}},{key:"renderResult",value:function(){return o.a.createElement(C,Object.assign({},this.state,{quizResult:this.state.result}))}},{key:"render",value:function(){return o.a.createElement(c.a,null,o.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"App-header"},o.a.createElement("img",{src:j.a,className:"App-logo",alt:"logo"}),o.a.createElement("h2",{style:{color:"#CFDE00"}}," ",this.state.quizzTitle)),this.state.result?this.renderResult():this.renderQuiz()),o.a.createElement(h.c,null,o.a.createElement(h.a,{path:"/winners",component:P})))}}]),t}(r.Component);function F(e,t){return o.a.createElement("p",{key:t},e)}var P=function(e){function t(){return Object(l.a)(this,t),Object(p.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(y.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e,t=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("emails"));return t||(e=o.a.createElement("p",null,"No winners to display")),t&&(e=t.map(F)),o.a.createElement(w.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container result",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500},o.a.createElement("h2",null,"Winners"),e)}}]),t}(r.Component),_=R;Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));i.a.render(o.a.createElement(c.a,null,o.a.createElement(_,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()}))}},[[124,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.e408f7ff.chunk.js.map